powerpoetry.org 2017-12-20

# Privacy Policy | Power Poetry

**Privacy Policy**

PowerPoetry.org and its affiliates and sublicensees ("Producer", "We", or "Us") offers an online youth poetry platform (the  “Service”) through its website currently located at Powerpoetry.org, which exact URL may change from time to time (the "Site ").  If applicable, you may be required to set up an account to access the portions of Site or Service that allow the downloading of films and videos. You are responsible for your use of the Site and Service, for any content (and personal information) you post to the Site or Service, and for any consequences thereof. Any content you submit, post, or display (the “Content”) will be able to be viewed by other users of the Site and Service and through third-party services and websites. You should only provide Content that you are comfortable sharing with others under the terms of this Privacy Policy.  This Privacy Policy is incorporated into, and forms a part of, the terms of use agreement between the parties (the “Agreement”).

I. We may collect information from you:  You agree that We may collect and store information about you when you open an account, upload content, participate on the Site or Service, communicate with customer service, or send Us an email. Such information may include your name, address, phone number, and email address. If anything is purchased by you on the Site or Service, We may also collect and store all information related to the purchase.  Our server logs automatically receives and records information from your browser, such as your IP address, your browser type and language, the page you request, and the date and time of your visit, which helps Us track users’ movements around our site and understand trends.  Like most websites, We may assign your computer one or more cookies which may collect information to facilitate access to our website and to personalize your online experience. We may use standard Internet tools, such as web beacons, which collect information that tracks your use of our website and enables Us to customize our services.   We will retain and use your information as long as We desire or as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce this Agreement.  We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. Should We ever do so, We will comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act.  

a. “IP Addresses”

IP Addresses are automatically reported by your browser each time you view a web page.  Your IP address is stored in our user registration database when you register with the “Site.”

IP Addresses may be used for various purposes, including:

1. To diagnose or service technology problems reported by our users or engineers that are associated with the IP addresses controlled by a specific web company or ISP.

2. To tailor advertising based on geographic area or other information derived from your IP address. Aggregate information derived from IP addresses may also be reported to advertisers.

3. To estimate the total number of users visiting the Site from specific geographical regions.

b. “Cookies”

A cookie is a small amount of data which often includes an anonymous unique identifier, and it is sent to your browser from a web site's computer and stored on your computer's hard drive.

You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set.

(If applicable) If you reject all cookies, you will not be able to use the products or services that require you to "sign in" and you may not be able to take full advantage of the Service.

(If applicable) The Site uses its own cookies for a number of purposes, including to:

1. Access your information when you "sign in".

2. Keep track of preferences you specify while you are using our Services.

3. Display the most appropriate advertising banners, based on your interests and activity on the Site. 

4. Estimate and report our total audience size and traffic.

5. Conduct research to improve the Site’s content and services.

(If applicable) We may let other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other entities' use of their cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, and is not subject to this privacy policy. Advertisers or other entities do not have access to our cookies.

II. We may use and disclose information in certain situations: 

a. You agree that We may use information to: access your information when you “sign in”; customize content on our Site or Service; facilitate use of our Site or Service, including any purchases relating thereto; manage your account and your preferences; analyze use of and improve our Site or Service, products and services related thereto; identify and protect against fraudulent transactions and other misuses of our Site or Service; enforce our Agreeement; protect the rights and safety of Us, our shareholders, members, officers, employees and customers; at our option, to notify you of any changes to this Privacy Policy or our other terms and conditions of this Site or Service (you are bound by the terms of any changes We post to our Site or Service whether or not We notify you by email) and as otherwise required by law. 

b. We disclose your information to third parties only as reasonably required for the above purposes or to protect our rights and safety, and those of our shareholders, members, employees and customers (such as to legal representatives and law enforcement) as you expressly permit and as required by law (such as the result of a subpoena, warrant, court order, or legal process).  

c. It may be necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities, including without limitation, fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Our terms of use, or as otherwise permitted or required by law.  

d. We may transfer your information in the event of the sale of substantially all of the assets of our business to a third-party, or in the event of a merger, consolidation or acquisition. However, in such event, any acquirer will be subject to the provisions of our commitments to you. We may also share aggregated, non-personal information in any of the above situations and also with others.  In this event, We will notify you by email or by putting a prominent notice on the Site before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.  

III. Your Options:  You have the choice to: not provide personal information, although that may result in your inability to use the Site, Services, or obtain certain services, or use certain features of our Site or Services; stop receiving promotional emails or newsletters from Us by sending an email to the contact address at the bottom of this policy; delete or decline cookies by changing your browser settings, although if you do so, some of the features or services of our Site or Services may not function properly; and/or review and update your personal information by contacting Us at the email address below or, if you have an online account on our Site or Services, by logging into that account. 

a. “Editing and Deleting Account Information; Security”

You can change your Account Information at any time.

You can delete your account at any time from your account page; however, please note that your identification, billing and contact information may remain in Our records for some period.

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

Your Account Information is password-protected.

IV. The Google Analytics features Power Poetry has implemented is based on Display Advertising (e.g., Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, the DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration, or Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting).

Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads using the [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads?hl=en&sig=ACi0TCjnLIRO_qykNCRIpCzO72Yw_vwH6H-aG6QU06CCG609PSlGKDeR7pkJ30frrmxc0XuM3AbFoa6DjMzJ6ivXcG2yjMsFZeyMQu8lugQ-DFtCIpyXxsPPkDCrEYOMDUhCuMdX9D9_5bwGxksPpHHZAGU3rea0DqZvKFWsBR57EUQzrGfR90QW9hNkTeVOkegHWzG5zeIxkT2z63ddiKg1k1kkdWU5Fw).

Power Poetry will not facilitate the merging of personally-identifiable information with non-personally identifiable information previously collected from Display Advertising features that is based on the DoubleClick cookie unless you have robust notice of, and the user's prior affirmative (i.e., opt-in) consent to, that merger.

V. Notification of Changes:  Any changes in our Privacy Policy will be posted to the Site or Service and will become effective as of the date of posting with respect to information We then collect in the future, but will not be changed with respect to information that We have then already collected. It is and will be your responsibility to review our Privacy Policy from time to time to make sure you are aware of any changes.

VI. Effective Date:  The effective date of this policy is 2/4/2012.  

VII. Questions: If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy, feel free to contact Us by email or postal mail below:

PowerPoetry.org
